[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Before we get to that, how would you categorize where she is now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, she's in a different prison in reality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "How does she deal with that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, she's -- she accepts her reality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Have you formed any kind of opinion about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, I don't think anybody killed her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "What kind of woman is she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, she's a young woman, just slightly older than some of my grandchildren.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "They perform, didn't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Judges, clerks, deputies, witnesses, lawyers, jurors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Could she be pulling the wool over your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, I guess anything is possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "What will she be doing tomorrow for example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Well, she will read books.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "You think she'd like to be a mother again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "She probably would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Lisa, what did you make of it today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I found the testimony incredibly moving.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Is it significant that his story is slightly changing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "It would be if he were the sole witness or if he were the victim.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "In your experience in this field, it can't be uncommon that a 14-year-old boy would perhaps have memory issues with this kind of thing, could it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Doty"]}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "What is their importance in this now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I think Doty's importance is clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "In relation to Joe Paterno?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Well, it's a tragedy because it shows what happens when you have an icon and when football becomes too important at a university.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "You mean \"Dallas,\" not the royal wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Actually both were.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Was it all you hoped it would be when you signed up for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "More.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Really, why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "We had this realization we would never work together again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "I mean, you look so nice and normal today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Were you remotely concerned, given that you were the top dog, if you like, that it might damage the brand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "How long did you think about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "About until they told me how much I was going to make.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "How much was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "I don't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "How much did the friendship come into it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't be doing it without them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Is everything OK, back to normal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "So far, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Was that your chuckle or was it one you perfected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "In Germany, it's not my chuckle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Did you really say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "He said that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "You think that's evil?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "No wonder I drank.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Did you like being, for what you were for a long time, the most evil man on television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Well, you know, I don't think I was an evil man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "That is evil, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Especially against his own family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Did you like the reputation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Of course I do, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["J.R."]}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "WP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "How do people react even now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "They -- the question they say is who shot J.R.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "You ever tell them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Yes, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bing Crosby"]}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "What did you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Bing Crosby's daughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "When you guys are filming in Dallas, presuming you live there for the duration, when you walk around, it must be like the royal family, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.K."]}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Where are you most popular outside America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I think it was in the U.K.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Every night, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Well, I actually was completely excited about what I considered to be a fun challenge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Ross"]}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Is he everything like his father or nothing like his father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "John Ross was a little baby.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Am I right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "How have you found it coming into this iconic show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "It's been wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1980"]}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "How old were you when \"Dallas\" -- how old are you, if you don't mind me asking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "``", "NNP", "''", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "I was born in 1980.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Jesse, for you, from \"Desperate House Wives\" to \"Dallas,\" does it get any better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "TO", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "You know, I feel incredibly blessed to have the opportunity to be another television phenomenon.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Can we have a little critique?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "They're going to drag us into another 13 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]